Register of the Robert Charles Hill papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- U.S. Department of State File, 1954-1958
  - Subject file, 1955-1957
    - U.S. Congress, 1956-1957
      - Correspondence, 1955-1957
        - House of Representatives
          - Holt, Joe, 1957 (Box-folder 25: 52)
          - Hope, Clifford R., 1956 (Box-folder 25: 53)
          - Hosmer, Craig, 1957 (Box-folder 25: 54)
          - Jackson, Donald L., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 25: 55)
          - Jarman, John, 1957 (Box-folder 25: 56)
          - Judd, Walter H., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 25: 57)
          - Keating, Kenneth B., 1956 (Box-folder 25: 58)
          - Kee, Elizabeth, 1956 (Box-folder 25: 59)
          - Kelly, Edna F., 1956 (Box-folder 25: 60)
          - Keogh, Eugene J., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 25: 61)
          - Kilgore, Joe M., 1956 (Box-folder 25: 62)
          - LeCompte, Karl M., 1956 (Box-folder 25: 63)
          - Lennon, Alton, 1957 (Box-folder 25: 64)
          - McCormack, John W., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 25: 65)
          - McIntire, Clifford G., 1957 (Box-folder 25: 66)
          - Martin, Joseph W., Jr., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 25: 67)
          - Merrow, Chester E., 1955-1956 (Box-folder 25: 68)
          - Morano, Albert P., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 25: 69)
          - Morgan, Thomas E., 1956 (Box-folder 25: 70)
          - Morris, Toby, 1957 (Box-folder 25: 71)
          - Multer, Abraham J., 1956 (Box-folder 25: 72)
          - O'Brien, Leo W., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 1)
          - O'Hara, Barratt, 1957 (Box-folder 26: 2)
          - O'Hara, Joseph P., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 3)
          - Patterson, James T., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 4)
          - Pelly, Thomas M., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 5)
          - Pillion, John R., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 6)
          - Powell, Adam Clayton, Jr., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 7)
          - Preston, Prince H., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 8)
          - Price, Melvin, 1957 (Box-folder 26: 9)
          - Prouty, Winston L., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 10)
          - Ray, John H., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 11)
          - Rayburn, Sam, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 12)
          - Reece, Carroll, 1955-1957 (Box-folder 26: 13)
          - Reed, Daniel A., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 14)
          - Rhodes, John J., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 15)
          - Richards, James P., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 16)
          - Rivers, L. Mendel, 1956 (Box-folder 26: 17)
          - Rooney, John J., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 18)
          - Saund, D. S., 1957 (Box-folder 26: 19)
          - Scott, Hugh, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 20)
          - Selden, Armistead I., Jr., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 21)
          - Short, Dewey, 1956 (Box-folder 26: 22)
          - Sikes, Bob, 1956 (Box-folder 26: 23)
          - Smith, Lawrence H., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 24)
          - Staggers, Harley O., 1957 (Box-folder 26: 25)
          - Taber, John, 1956 (Box-folder 26: 26)
          - Talle, Henry O., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 27)
          - Teague, Charles M., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 28)
          - Un-American Activities Committee, 1956 (Box-folder 26: 29)
          - Van Zandt, James E., 1957 (Box-folder 26: 30)
          - Vorys, John M., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 31)
          - Whitten, Jamie L., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 32)
          - Wigglesworth, Richard B., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 33)
          - Williams, Harrison A., Jr., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 34)
          - Wolcott, Jesse P., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 35)
          - Wolverton, Charles A., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 36)
          - Yates, Sidney R., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 37)
          - Young, Clifton, 1956 (Box-folder 26: 38)
        - Senate
          - Aiken, George D., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 39)
          - Bennett, Wallace F., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 40)
          - Bible, Alan, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 41)
          - Bridges, Styles, 1955-1957 (Box-folder 26: 42)
          - Butler, John Marshall, 1957 (Box-folder 26: 43)
          - Capehart, Homer E., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 44)
          - Carlson, Frank, 1956 (Box-folder 26: 45)
          - Committee on the Judiciary. Internal Security Subcommittee, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 46)
          - Cooper, John Sherman, 1956 (Box-folder 26: 47)
          - Cotton, Norris, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 48)
          - Curtis, Carl T., 1957 (Box-folder 26: 49)
          - Dirksen, Everett McKinley, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 50)
          - Douglas, Paul H., 1957 (Box-folder 26: 51)
          - Eastland, James O., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 52)
          - Ellender, Allen, 1956 (Box-folder 26: 53)
          - Fulbright, J. W., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 54)
          - George, Walter F., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 55)
          - Goldwater, Barry, 1957 (Box-folder 26: 56)
          - Green, Theodore Francis, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 57)
          - Hickenlooper, Bourke B., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 58)
          - Holland, Spessard L., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 59)
          - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 60)
          - Humphreys, Robert, 1956 (Box-folder 26: 61)
          - Ives, Irving M., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 62)
          - Javits, Jacob K., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 63)
          - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 64)
          - Johnston, Olin D., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 65)
          - Kennedy, John F., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 66)
          - Knowland, William F., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 67)
          - Kuchel, Thomas H., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 68)
          - Langer, William, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 69)
          - Lehman, Herbert H., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 70)
          - Long, Russell B., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 71)
          - McSweeney, Joseph B., 1957 (Box-folder 26: 72)
          - Mansfield, Mike, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 73)
          - Martin, Thomas E., 1957 (Box-folder 26: 74)
          - Millikin, Eugene D., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 75)
          - Morton, Thruston B., 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 76)
          - O'Mahoney, Joseph C., 1957 (Box-folder 26: 77)
          - Payne, Frederick G., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 78)
          - Republican Policy Committee, 1957 (Box-folder 26: 79)
          - Revercomb, Chapman, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 80)
          - Robertson, A. Willis, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 81)
          - Russell, Richard B., 1956 (Box-folder 26: 82)
          - Saltonstall, Leverett, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 83)
          - Smathers, George, 1956 (Box-folder 26: 84)
          - Smith, H. Alexander, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 85)
          - Sparkman, John, 1956 (Box-folder 26: 86)
          - Symington, Stuart, 1956 (Box-folder 26: 87)
          - Talmadge, Herman E., 1957 (Box-folder 26: 88)
          - Wiley, Alexander, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 26: 89)
      - Publications, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 27: 1-2)
    - U.S. Department of State, Bureau of Security and Consular Affairs. Correspondence, and memoranda, 1955-1957 (Box-folder 27: 3)
  - Telephone numbers, undated (Box-folder 27: 4)
- Ambassador to Mexico File, 1956-1961
  Correspondence, speeches, memoranda, clippings, appointment books, press releases, printed matter, notes, schedules, reports, and despatches, arranged by form.
  - Appointment books - Clippings, 1957-1960
    - Appointment books, 1957-1959
      - 1957 (Box-folder 27: 5)
      - 1958 (Box-folder 27: 6)
      - 1959 (Box-folder 27: 7)
    - Biographical data. Writings, sketches, letters, notes, press releases, and questionnaires, 1957-1960 (Box-folder 28: 1)
    - Calling cards, undated (Box-folder 28: 2)
    - Chronological file of speeches and engagements, 1957-1960
      - List of visits, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 28: 3)
      - List of visits, memorandum, and letter, 1957 (Box-folder 28: 4)
      - Visit by Milton S. Eisenhower to Mexico, Schedules, correspondence, memoranda, clippings, and press release, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 28: 5)
      - American Society of Mexico meeting, Mexico City, Letter, 1957 August (Box-folder 28: 6)
      - Sales Executive Club luncheon, Mexico City, Correspondence, memoranda, clippings, program, press release, and speech, 1957 September (Box-folder 28: 7)
      - Eastern Air Lines inaugural New York-Mexico City flight, Memoranda, 1957 September (Box-folder 28: 8)
      - Visit to Mexico City College, Correspondence, and memorandum, 1957 October (Box-folder 28: 9)
      - Visit to Tlaxcala, Mexico, Correspondence, memoranda, and schedule, 1957 October (Box-folder 28: 10)
      - Statement to Instituto Mexicano Norteamericano de Relaciones Culturales, Statement, 1957 October (Box-folder 28: 11)
      - Visit to Hermosillo, Mexico, Correspondence, 1957 November (Box-folder 29: 1)
      - Girl Scouts talk, Mexico City, Letter, 1957 November (Box-folder 29: 2)
      - Visit to sugar refinery, Xicothencatl, Mexico, Memoranda, 1957 November (Box-folder 29: 3)
      - American Legion meeting, Mexico City, Clipping, 1957 November (Box-folder 29: 4)
      - Sierra Nevada School graduation exercises, Mexico City, Clipping, and speech, 1957 November (Box-folder 29: 5)
      - Visit to International Civil Aviation Organization Center, Mexico City, Memorandum, 1957 November (Box-folder 29: 6)
      - American Society of Mexico dance, Mexico City, Correspondence, 1957 November (Box-folder 29: 7)
      - Thanksgiving Day sermon, Union Evangelical Church, Mexico City, Correspondence, proclamation, and sermon, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 29: 8)
      - St. Andrew's Society dinner, British Club, Mexico City, Correspondence, memoranda, program, clipping, and speech, 1957 November (Box-folder 29: 9)
      - Visit to Washington, D.C., Correspondence, memoranda, despatches, schedules, and clippings, 1957 December (Box-folder 29: 10)
      - Washington Board of Trade meeting, Washington, D.C., Correspondence, despatches, memoranda, clipping, and speech, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 29: 11)
      - Interview, Houston, Texas, Clipping, 1957 December (Box-folder 29: 12)
      - Visit to Matamoros, Mexico, Correspondence, memoranda, schedules, and clippings, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 29: 13)
      - Correspondence, despatches, memoranda, schedules, clippings, and notes, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 29: 14)
      - National Museum of Anthropology presentation, Mexico City, Correspondence, notes, and speech, 1958 January (Box-folder 29: 15)
      - Visit to U.S. border consulates, Mexico, Correspondence, memoranda, schedules, and clippings, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 29: 16)
      - Visit to U.S. consulates, Mexico, Correspondence, memoranda, schedules, lists, and calling cards, 1958 (Box-folder 29: 17)
      - Visit to Washington, D.C., and New York City, Letters, and memorandum, 1958 March (Box-folder 29: 18)
      - Visit to U.S. consulates, Mexico, Correspondence, memoranda, and schedules, 1958 March (Box-folder 30: 1)
      - National Association of Importers and Exporters luncheon, Mexico City, Memoranda, programs, and speech, 1958 April (Box-folder 30: 2)
      - United Community Fund [of Americans in Mexico] radio broadcast, Leaflet, notes, and broadcast text, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 30: 3)
      - American Club Handicap presentation, Mexico City, Correspondence, memoranda, and clipping, 1958 April (Box-folder 30: 4)
      - Interview, Mexico City, Memorandum, and interview transcript, 1958 April (Box-folder 30: 5)
      - Visit to Monclova, Mexico, Correspondence, and memoranda, 1958 April (Box-folder 30: 6)
      - Visit to Austin, Texas, Correspondence, 1958 April (Box-folder 30: 7)
      - Rotary Club luncheon, Houston, Texas, Correspondence, memoranda, notes, despatches, clippings, press releases, and speech, 1958 April (Box-folder 30: 8)
      - Rotary Club luncheon, San Antonio, Texas, Correspondence, memoranda, clipping, and speech, 1958 April (Box-folder 30: 9)
      - Royal Society of St. George dinner, British Club, Mexico City, Memoranda, notes, and program, 1958 April (Box-folder 30: 10)
      - Interview, Mexico City, Correspondence, 1958 April (Box-folder 30: 11)
      - Inauguration of President Mario Echandi Jimenez, San Jose, Costa Rica, Correspondence, despatches, program, schedule, notes, clipping, and bulletin, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 30: 12)
      - Visit to Miami, Fla., Correspondence, despatches, and notes, 1958 May (Box-folder 30: 13)
      - Young Men's Christian Association luncheon, Miami, Fla., Correspondence, 1958 May (Box-folder 30: 14)
      - Memorial Day services, Mexico City, Correspondence, memoranda, notes, program, clippings, and speech, 1958 May (Box-folder 30: 15)
      - Western Shrine Association convention, Mexico City, Correspondence, memoranda, notes, program, and speech, 1958 May (Box-folder 30: 16)
      - American Society in Mexico Community Fund drive, Letters, memorandum, and statement, 1958 June (Box-folder 30: 17)
      - Rotary International convention, Dallas, Texas, Correspondence, despatches, memoranda, notes, clippings, and speech, 1958 June (Box-folder 30: 18)
      - Shrimp Association of the Americas convention, Mexico City, Correspondence, and notes, 1958 June (Box-folder 31: 1)
      - Consular conference [for U.S. consuls in Mexico], Mexico City, Correspondence, memoranda, press releases, agenda, and information booklet, 1958 June (Box-folder 31: 2)
      - American School graduation exercises, Mexico City, Correspondence, memoranda, notes, program, and speech, 1958 June (Box-folder 31: 3)
      - Independence Day celebration, American School, Mexico City, Correspondence, memoranda, notes, program, clippings, press releases, and speech, 1958 June (Box-folder 31: 4)
      - Independence Day service, Christ Church, Mexico City, Correspondence, and program, 1958 June (Box-folder 31: 5)
      - Independence Day statement, Mexico City, Correspondence, despatches, memoranda, notes, schedule, and statement, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 31: 6)
      - Associated General Contractors of America dinner, Mexico City, Correspondence, and memoranda, 1958 July (Box-folder 31: 7)
      - Visit to Washington, D.C., Correspondence, memoranda, despatches, programs, and clipping, 1958 July (Box-folder 31: 8)
      - Business Council for International Understanding luncheon, Washington, D.C., Correspondence, memoranda, notes, program, reports, and printed matter, 1956-1958 (Box-folder 31: 9)
      - Confederation of Chambers of Commerce luncheon, Mexico City, Despatches, and program, 1958 July (Box-folder 31: 10)
      - Comite Norteamericano Pro-Mexico luncheon, Mexico City, Correspondence, memoranda, and program, 1958 July (Box-folder 31: 11)
      - Instituto Mexicano Norteamericano de Relaciones Culturales talk, Mexico City, Letter, memorandum, and program, 1958 July (Box-folder 31: 12)
      - Mexican Association of Veterans of World War II ceremony, Mexico City, Memoranda, and clippings, 1958 July (Box-folder 31: 13)
      - American Legion convention, Guadalajara, Mexico, Correspondence, memoranda, notes, program, and speech, 1958 July (Box-folder 31: 14)
      - Organization of American States Inter-American Travel Congresses Technical Committee on Travel Promotion meeting, Mexico City, Speech, 1958 July (Box-folder 31: 15)
      - American Chamber of Commerce of Mexico annual meeting, Mexico City, Correspondence, memoranda, notes, program, clipping, and speech, 1958 August (Box-folder 31: 16)
      - Visit by U.S.S. Ranger to Acapulco, Mexico, Correspondence, despatches, memoranda, notes, and clippings, 1958 August (Box-folder 31: 17)
      - Visit to Miguel Aleman Hydroelectric System, Toluca, Mexico, Statement, 1958 August (Box-folder 31: 18)
      - Visit to Washington, D.C., and Baltimore, Md., Correspondence, despatches, memoranda, and notes, 1958 August - September (Box-folder 31: 19)
      - American School dedication, Monterrey, Mexico, Correspondence, memoranda, schedules, lists, bulletins, guide, and clippings, 1958 September (Box-folder 31: 20)
      - Visit to Arizona and California, Correspondence, despatches, memoranda, and schedule, 1958 September (Box-folder 31: 21)
      - American Institute for Foreign Trade talk, Phoenix, Ariz., Correspondence, and notes, 1958 September (Box-folder 31: 22)
      - World Affairs Council luncheon, Los Angeles, Cal., Correspondence, notes, clipping, and speech, 1958 September (Box-folder 31: 23)
      - Visit to southern Mexico, Correspondence, memoranda, notes, schedule, and map, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 31: 24)
      - World Film Festival, Mexico City, Correspondence, memoranda, and clippings, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 32: 1)
      - Radio interview, Mexico City, Memorandum, and note, 1958 October (Box-folder 32: 2)
      - Texas Rose Festival, Tyler, Texas, Correspondence, memoranda, notes, despatches, clippings, schedule, and speech, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 32: 3)
      - Visit to Pachuca, Mexico, Correspondence, notes, and schedule, 1958 October (Box-folder 32: 4)
      - International Road Federation meeting, Mexico City, Correspondence, memoranda, schedule, and bulletins, 1958 October (Box-folder 32: 5)
      - American Society of Travel Agents conference, Mexico City, Correspondence, memoranda, notes, schedule, press release, clippings, and speech, 1958 October (Box-folder 32: 6)
      - International Relations Club meeting, Mexico City College, Correspondence, note, and clipping, 1958 October (Box-folder 32: 7)
      - Visit to Salvatierra, Mexico, Correspondence, and notes, 1958 November (Box-folder 32: 8)
      - Visit by Eleanor Roosevelt to Mexico, Correspondence, memoranda, notes, and clippings, 1958 November (Box-folder 32: 9)
      - American School Parent-Teacher Association meeting, Mexico City, Letter, and note, 1958 November (Box-folder 32: 10)
      - Message to Congregational Church, Littleton, N.H., Letter, and message, 1958 November (Box-folder 32: 11)
      - Pan American Dental Congress, Mexico City, Correspondence, notes, program, and regulations, 1958 November (Box-folder 32: 12)
      - Thanksgiving Day sermon, Union Evangelical Church, Mexico City, Correspondence, program, and proclamation, 1958 November (Box-folder 32: 13)
      - Inauguration of President Adolfo Lopez Mateos, Mexico City, Correspondence, despatches, memoranda, notes, schedules, and clippings, 1958 December (Box-folder 32: 14)
      - Visit to Texas, Correspondence, memoranda, notes, and miscellany, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 32: 15)
      - Black and White Ball, San Antonio, Texas, Correspondence, despatches, notes, schedules, guide, and invitation, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 32: 16)
      - Statement on Drew Pearson article, Mexico City, Memorandum, notes, and statement, 1958 December (Box-folder 32: 17)
      - Visit to Washington, D.C., Despatches, and memoranda, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 32: 18)
      - Correspondence, despatches, memoranda, notes, schedules, writings, and clippings, 1959 (Box-folder 32: 19)
      - Comite Norteamericano Pro-Mexico annual meeting, Mexico City, Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 33: 1)
      - Visit to Compania Industrial de San Cristobal Pulp and Paper Mill, San Cristobal Ecatepec, Mexico, Correspondence, and notes, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 33: 2)
      - American School Teacher-Training Workshop for English Speaking Teachers, Mexico City, Memorandum, 1959 January (Box-folder 33: 3)
      - Message to Harvey Hile testimonial dinner, Washington, D.C., Correspondence, and message, 1959 January (Box-folder 33: 4)
      - Western Airlines Board of Directors meeting, Mexico City, Correspondence, 1959 February (Box-folder 33: 5)
      - Visit by President Dwight D. Eisenhower to Acapulco, Mexico, Correspondence, despatches, memoranda, notes, schedules, clippings, and printed communique, 1959 February (Box-folder 33: 6)
      - Washington's Birthday ceremony, Mexico City, Memoranda, 1959 February (Box-folder 33: 7)
      - Visit to Europe, Correspondence, despatches, memoranda, notes, report, schedules, press releases, clippings, printed matter, and miscellany, 1958-1960 (Box-folder 33: 8-9)
      - Caribbean and Central American Chiefs of Mission [of the U.S.] Conference, San Salvador, El Salvador, Correspondence, memoranda, schedules, and clippings, 1959 April (Box-folder 33: 10)
      - Visit by Pan American Commission of Tampa, Fla., to Mexico, Correspondence, memoranda, notes, and schedule, 1959 April (Box-folder 33: 11)
      - Defensores de la Republica Mexicana decoration, Mexico City, Correspondence, memoranda, notes, schedule, press release, clipping, and speech, 1959 April (Box-folder 33: 12)
      - Visit to CARE well-digging project, San Mateo Atenco, Mexico, Correspondence, notes, memoranda, bulletin, report, and miscellany, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 33: 13)
      - Visit to Acapulco, Mexico, Memoranda, 1959 May (Box-folder 33: 14)
      - Visit to Washington, D.C., Correspondence, and memoranda, 1959 May (Box-folder 33: 15)
      - American Institute for Foreign Trade graduation exercises, Phoenix, Ariz., Correspondence, memoranda, notes, program, clipping, bulletin, and speech, 1959 June (Box-folder 33: 16)
      - Mexico City College commencement, Correspondence, memoranda, notes, and schedule, 1959 June (Box-folder 33: 17)
      - Visit to north central Mexico, Correspondence, memoranda, notes, schedules, clippings, printed matter, and miscellany, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 34: 1-2)
      - Consular conference [for U.S. consuls in Mexico], Mexico City, Correspondence, memoranda, notes, and agenda, 1959 June (Box-folder 34: 3)
      - Garside School graduation exercises, Mexico City, Correspondence, memoranda, notes, program, clippings, and speech, 1959 June (Box-folder 34: 4)
      - National University of Mexico talk, Mexico City, Correspondence, memoranda, notes, clippings, and catalog, 1959 June (Box-folder 34: 5)
      - Statement on travel in Mexico, Statement, 1959 June (Box-folder 34: 6)
      - Independence Day statement, Mexico City, Correspondence, memoranda, clippings, miscellany, and statement, 1959 July (Box-folder 34: 7)
      - Statement to The News [Mexico City], Correspondence, memorandum, and clippings, 1959 July (Box-folder 34: 8)
      - Independence Day service, Christ Church, Mexico City, Correspondence, 1959 July (Box-folder 34: 9)
      - Rotary Club luncheon, Mexico City, Correspondence, memoranda, bulletin, and speech, 1959 July (Box-folder 34: 10)
      - Mobile Home Manufacturers Association convention, Mexico City, Correspondence, brochure, press release, and speech, 1959 July (Box-folder 34: 11)
      - Visit to Nexaca, Mexico, Correspondence, notes, and map, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 34: 12)
      - Defensores de la Republica Mexicana and American Legion luncheon, Mexico City, Letter, memoranda, schedule, press release, and speech, 1959 July (Box-folder 34: 13)
      - American Chamber of Commerce of Mexico luncheon, Mexico City, Correspondence, 1959 July (Box-folder 34: 14)
      - American Legion meeting, Mexico City, Correspondence, memoranda, and notes, 1959 July (Box-folder 34: 15)
      - Rotary Club meeting, Albuquerque, N. Mex., Correspondence, memoranda, notes, clippings, miscellany, and speech, 1959 July (Box-folder 35: 1)
      - Braniff International Airways dinner, Dallas, Texas, Correspondence, notes, clippings, and resolution, 1959 July (Box-folder 35: 2)
      - Visit to Oaxaca, Mexico, Program, and note, 1959 July (Box-folder 35: 3)
      - American community luncheon, Mexico City, Letter, and notes, 1959 July (Box-folder 35: 4)
      - Texas House of Representatives resolution, Correspondence, memoranda, and resolution, 1959 July (Box-folder 35: 5)
      - American Legion resolution, Correspondence, and notes, 1959 August (Box-folder 35: 6)
      - American Chamber of Commerce of Mexico dinner, Mexico City, Correspondence, memoranda, and notes, 1959 August (Box-folder 35: 7)
      - Visit to Campeche, Mexico, Correspondence, memorandum, and notes, 1959 August (Box-folder 35: 8)
      - Variety Club luncheon, Mexico City, Letter, note, and clipping, 1959 August (Box-folder 35: 9)